[{"answer": " How are you today, Kimeko", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Pretty good.  Thank you", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 13, "question": " How are you today, Kimeko", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Are you ready to start our tutoring today", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Pretty good.  Thank you", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Yes", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Are you ready to start our tutoring today", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Good.  The topic were going to talk about today is adventure.  Do you know wha", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Yes", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Ive heard it before, yes.  Doesnt it mean something fun or crazy", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Good.  The topic were going to talk about today is adventure.  Do you know wha", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Yes, it has to do with those things.  An adventure is an exciting experience, ofte", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Ive heard it before, yes.  Doesnt it mean something fun or crazy", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yes, Indiana Jones.  I know those movies  with Harrison Ford", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Yes, it has to do with those things.  An adventure is an exciting experience, ofte", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Yes, exactly.  Those movies are full of the adventures of Indiana Jones", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Yes, Indiana Jones.  I know those movies  with Harrison Ford", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " I remember he is always chasing villains, escaping explosions, and travelin", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Yes, exactly.  Those movies are full of the adventures of Indiana Jones", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Thats right.  So, have you ever had an adventure", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 35, "question": " I remember he is always chasing villains, escaping explosions, and travelin", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Let me think Yes, I think so.  Last summer", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Thats right.  So, have you ever had an adventure", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Can you tell me about it?  What did you do", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Let me think Yes, I think so.  Last summer", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Sure.  Last summer I went to a small island in Mexico", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Can you tell me about it?  What did you do", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " What was it called", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Sure.  Last summer I went to a small island in Mexico", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Im sorry, I cant recall", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 40, "question": " What was it called", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " No problem.  Go on", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Im sorry, I cant recall", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " We went there on kind of an adventure vacation", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 42, "question": " No problem.  Go on", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " That sounds exciting.  What did you do", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " We went there on kind of an adventure vacation", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Well, from the island, we took jet skis to another island in the middle of th", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 44, "question": " That sounds exciting.  What did you do", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Well, from the island, we took jet skis to another island in the middle of th", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Yes.  Once we reached this island we put on scuba gear and swa", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Underneath the island?  What do you mean", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yes.  Once we reached this island we put on scuba gear and swa", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Under the water, the island was full of caves so we swam under the island an", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Underneath the island?  What do you mean", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " How exciting!  What was in the caves", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Under the water, the island was full of caves so we swam under the island an", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " It was pretty scary, actually.  The caves were full of a rare kind of bat.  The", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 60, "question": " How exciting!  What was in the caves", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " A dog?  Thats huge", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 64, "question": " It was pretty scary, actually.  The caves were full of a rare kind of bat.  The", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " I know", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 65, "question": " A dog?  Thats huge", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Werent you scared they would bite you", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 66, "question": " I know", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " No, our guide said they only eat insects and seaweed, so I wasnt too scared", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Werent you scared they would bite you", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Im sure it did", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 74, "question": " No, our guide said they only eat insects and seaweed, so I wasnt too scared", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " While we were in the cave, we got to take pictures of the bats and we crawle", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Im sure it did", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " It sounds kind of dangerous", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 79, "question": " While we were in the cave, we got to take pictures of the bats and we crawle", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " It was a little.  My friend cut his leg on the sharp rocks.  But I was OK.  It wa", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 80, "question": " It sounds kind of dangerous", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " I never even knew they existed", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 84, "question": " It was a little.  My friend cut his leg on the sharp rocks.  But I was OK.  It wa", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Yes, they only live on this one island, so most people have never seen them", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 85, "question": " I never even knew they existed", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Well, you did have a great adventure, then", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Yes, they only live on this one island, so most people have never seen them", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yeah, it was a great adventure vacation", "docId": "08-03", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Well, you did have a great adventure, then", "qSentId": 86}]
